<CD-RAT><Entry><HWD>09\1\2\Sequencing devices</HWD><Activity><ColourWords layer="1" h="480" w="680" y="10" x="10" is-single-select="0"><Title alignment="left" isOn="1">Sequencing devices<br /></Title><Instruction alignment="left" isOn="1">There are eight mistakes in the text. Click on the mistakes.<br /></Instruction><ReferenceObject soundIsOn="0" videoIsOn="0" defaultHeight="200" alignment="left" isOn="0" /><ScrollableAssets /><Content><Sentence>I often get into a panic at airports, but my most recent experience was a classic example! After <SelectString is-correct="1"><Score num="1" />arrive</SelectString> at the airport with my girlfriend, we queued up at the check-in desk and got our boarding passes. Having <SelectString is-correct="1"><Score num="1" />get</SelectString> our boarding passes, we went through the security gate. While <SelectString is-correct="1"><Score num="1" />gone</SelectString> through the metal detector, I suddenly heard a loud alarm and saw lots of flashing lights. Before <SelectString is-correct="1"><Score num="1" />allow</SelectString> me through, the security officer insisted on searching me thoroughly. I had forgotten that there was a penknife in my pocket. It was very embarrassing! <br /><br />After that we went through to the departure gate and waited for our flight. While <SelectString is-correct="1"><Score num="1" />waited</SelectString>, we decided to have a snack and some coffee.  <SelectString is-correct="1"><Score num="1" />Had</SelectString>finished our snack, we went to look at the duty free shops. We chose some French perfume and I went to the cash desk to pay while my girlfriend went to the toilet. On <SelectString is-correct="1"><Score num="1" />reach</SelectString> into my pocket to get out my card, I realised it wasn't there. I was sure I had had it with me when I arrived at the airport. Then I remembered. Before <SelectString is-correct="1"><Score num="1" />go</SelectString> through the metal detector, I had given my wallet to my girlfriend. So I had to wait for her to come back from the toilet before I could pay. Yet again I felt like a complete idiot!</Sentence></Content></ColourWords><Feedback playallOn="1" showAnswersOn="1" animatedFeedbackOn="1" testModeOn="0" instantFeedbackOn="0"><Sounds /></Feedback><GenericActivity timerIsOn="0" CDPrefsFolder="" CDPrefsFile="cd.xml"><ActivityCanvas graphicAlpha="100" folder="" file="" colourAlpha="100" colour="transparent" /><SoundLibrary y="10" x="10" isOn="0" /><VideoLibrary h="252" w="385" y="78" x="10" isOn="0" /><Assets /></GenericActivity></Activity></Entry></CD-RAT>